So the reason I came across all those IDs and VIP passes and talent badges and Alex's passes
that I posted earlier was because I was building my altar. I was putting together my altar and I
was looking for my grandmother's journal to put on my altar. And so I was looking through these
different boxes I have. And I've been at work for so long, y'all. And I think a lot of people
don't know that. And I think it's like on one hand, I'd be like,
how y'all niggas don't know me? And then on the other hand, I'm just like,
well, their folks are meeting a new me at a new time. And I had a little fear today because I
was like planning my future. And I realized like, you're trying to plan for May and June
and you know full well that there is a likelihood that May and June will not be the world you're in
today. And a lot of the shifting that continues to happen with me is moving outside of the practices,
the habits, the cycles that I was, you know, so that I was trained in for so long. What you saw
in that post, that's 33 years of work. I've been working and that's only since I was 12. I've been
working since I was eight. I've been working since I was, oh my God, I have chocolate all over myself.
I'm glutton. Murphy, I don't support governors. I don't, I'm not even in California. I don't vote
in California. So I'm not supporting any governors. I don't support establishment politics.
So you have to understand that. I did eat it off myself, Liz. You watched it happen in real time.
Yeah, I just, I just, I wanted to share my feelings because I feel like a lot of y'all
probably feel the same way, which is like the instability halts your feelings of being able
to plan, to envision, to dream, to wonder. Um, and I can tell you that there's one thing about
wondering and there's one thing about imagining, but then the next phase is planning. And when your
planning is disrupted, if you're a planner, it's, it's, it's jarring because you're like, well,
what are we, what are we even doing? What are we even doing? And so it just, it really, it really
like shook me up and it really made me say like, you need to reimagine how you plan and, and the ways
that you're, you're used to planning. I can feel it in my diaphragm right now, my solar plexus, like
I'm onto something. I'm onto something. I just, I have to lean into it. I went and sat with the trees
today. And, um, I was, I started reading this book. Um, so basically I, I've been trying to like
go outside and read this book by the trees. And, um, it's, I don't know why it's not trying to show
out, show the book. I'm trying to show y'all the book. And Instagram is like, no, you can't show
them books because then they'll read and we can't have that. Um, but I, I guess I just wanted to share
my feelings because, um, I know that I look, I know that I come off very confident on here
in a way that makes it seem like I've got it all figured out. And I don't, I don't have it all
figured out. I don't have anything really figured out other than who the fuck is fucking with us.
And, um, you know, that's a new revelation, you know, being able to identify, oh, that the
world bank and that the international monetary fund are behind the international energy association.
They are all in cahoots and they are the ones that are rolling out what we are going to experience
within the next few months. And for the record, they're already doing it in other places. Okay.
They're already rolling out different closures and, um, remote work mandates, et cetera, et cetera.
And they're doing this in, you know, places like, uh, Pakistan, Thailand, Vietnam, Malaysia,
the EU, Cambodia, they're doing this and they're setting things and they're setting things up. And,
you know, when people are so set bent on Trump and Democrats, et cetera, et cetera,
you're, you, you have to understand that they are ruled by a bigger force and that force rules the
world. And you see it when you see the world responding simultaneously. And I was saying this
yesterday and it's like, like, why would the president of the Philippines be doing an announcement
in English? So, you know, I'm just, to all my artists out there, the astrology girlies will tell you
that April is set up to like, try to break us. April is set up to try to break us. And, and yet
it is like celestially set up to fortify us for everything on the other side. And this is because
like all the planets are like out of retrograde at the same time. And in, um, and in Aries and like
Chiron as well. So like the astrology girlies are like, yeah, April is coming for that ass.
However, hold yes. Hold on, do it. Hold on, do it. No weapon formed against me shall prosper.
No, it won't work. So I'm going to tell y'all what I have to remind myself, which is like
the test is expected and it's necessary. And so stay the course, do not let doubt creep in
and deny you of your joy. Do not let doubt creep in and rob you of your strength. Do not let doubt
creep in and, um, convince you that we are not fortified. It is, it is so easy.
Cause I do this all the time. It is so easy to convince ourselves like, well, it's been screwed
up before and it never got fixed. And we can't give into that. We can't give into that because that
commits ourselves to the cycle and we got to break the cycle. So we can't, we can't give into,
well, it's been before we can't. That's why it becomes very dangerous to keep calling on
the civil rights leaders of the past as like, well, they did. We are the continuance,
not the culmination. So, you know, I just wanted to speak into y'all while I speak into myself,
speaking to y'all while I speak into myself, I'm going to take me,
I'm going to take me a, um, an Epsom salt bath and I'm going to take me, um,
I'm going to take a moment in front of my altar and talk to my ancestors. I've been taking my time
building my altar. And so now this will be the first time that I actually like speak to it.
And I think, I think honestly, our biggest challenge to be quite, our biggest challenge
is going to be believing in ourselves. That is our biggest challenge because there's, there's not
as many of us as there needs to be that are here. However, we have to remain here in order for those
numbers to grow. I don't know what the ancestry money is, but tell me what it is. That to me is
our biggest challenge. My altar, I'm not even sure if I'm supposed to tell y'all this, but I'm
gonna tell y'all anyway. My altar consists of soil that a homegirl brought me from Harriet Tubman's
grave. It consists of soil from, um, Palestine. It consists of two good luck purses from Korea that
each have a nutmeg in them because I don't, it's, it's not about gaining wealth and money right now for
me. It's about gaining wealth and knowledge of the land and of my ancestry. And that is Grenada.
Um, it consists of two white candles, one that has Harriet Tubman on it, one that has James Baldwin on it.
It consists of a book by Che Guevara that I got in Cuba. It consists of a book, uh, about Malcolm X that
I got in Cuba. Um, it exists, it consists of a picture of my grandmother and a card that she wrote me
for my 10th birthday. Um, it consists of a picture of my cat Lando who passed away. It consists of,
um, rock salt from Grenada. Um, sage. I'm not gonna have two separate altars. I believe that
they're in me. So that's what it's going to be. Um, and Murphy for CCC. I just hope that you stay
a small town council member because that's where the fight is actually happening in the small towns,
the fight. Once you get beyond the small town, you're no longer fighting for the people you're
fighting for your integrity and you're going to lose. So for all of y'all out there who are,
you know, working in small town politics, I hope that you understand that even in small towns,
there's corruption, but it's easier for you to remain true to the public servitude because you
are seeing the people you're serving. And the goal has always been for so many to like climb a ladder.
And that's not that you're literally climbing a ladder to nowhere. That's why when people ask me
about governor and shit like that, I'm like, well, then people are bought and sold.
They've already decided who the next governor of California is. Y'all aren't going to be able to
do an upset. They've already decided. First of all, California is super Zionist. It's also the fourth
largest GDP in the world. They've already decided who the winner is. Gavin Newsom or like it's already
decided. So it's, it's like, it's like if they drain your energy because they end up pulling your energy
into, um, feudal efforts. That's what they've been doing with black women and Democrats for the past,
how many years? They've gotten all these black women's incredible energy, their incredible loyalty,
their wisdom, their innovation, and they have sucked it dry. Democrats have been doing that.
And black women, Democrats have been encouraging black women, Democrats to do it. Meanwhile,
voting rights activists will tell you all day long that Democrats don't give a fuck about voting rights
and then go back to being in your face, telling you that you need to vote or else tea.
And I say, what am I doing? What is this? I spent three hours nonstop working on my,
um, working, working on my storage space. Okay. So someone here said, Mom Donnie made a difference,
right? So something I want y'all to really understand is that so many of you all are so easily pleased
by immediacy because the United States trains you to only care about immediacy and convenience.
You don't think in long-term, you think in now term, right? So, so many people is, um, so many,
so like this person here, GT gal 84 is trying to disrupt my point of view. Um, because she seems to
think that Zora Mamdani wasn't chosen. Zora Mamdani and Chris Cuomo were neck and neck. And I,
I promise you if they didn't want Mamdani to win, he would not have won. He literally changed his
behavior once it became possible. Yeah, I'm talking about you. He changed his behavior once it became
possible because it was like, you got to do this. If you're trying to win, you got to kiss the ring.
He started saying things like global intifada is, you know, a nasty word. He started capitulating.
He started showing up to Shabbat Lubavitch, you know, celebrations, et cetera, et cetera.
And so what I want y'all to understand is that the instant gratification that you are shown
is, is merely to shut you up. And because you don't demand long-term graduate gratification,
there's no reason for them to present it. Mamdani has been in the, I'm coming for you. Mamdani
has been in the office for 2.2 seconds. Y'all done had one half winter with Mamdani and you're
like, he made a difference. Okay. Okay. He came out here and got people to shovel snow. Okay.
That's positive. It is not long-term change. And because we are so easily appeased,
we don't demand long-term change. What we should be doing is saying, good.
What are you doing next? It's like y'all give niggas that you're dating a harder time than the
politicians that ask for you to give them power. I know women that will, a dude will be going over
the moon for them. And rightly so they're like, I mean, that's cute, but what else? Okay. But what
else? But what else? But see, you're not even listening to me because you're talking about,
he's finding common sense solutions and you're thinking only in terms of yourself. Was it a
common sense solution to, uh, not impede the continued sale of Palestinian land in the West
Bank and in, um, temples while allowing for there to be laws that prevent the protesting of this
outside of temples? Mark Lamont Hill is not a liberal. Don't come in here saying people's names
when you are behind a fake name and no picture. I just want y'all to understand who you're talking
to. Do not come in here and speak on people. I know while you behind a fake name and a picture
and a no picture. You don't get to do that. Thank you. Doc, Doc, Doc, Doc B. Darrow. You got to be
a, and what else? You got to be a, and what else? I mean, there's a whole Destiny's Child song
called, Can You Pay My Bill? I don't know if those are the words, but it's about bills. That is the
energy that we should be having for politicians. I don't think you do. You talk about you love Mom
Donnie. I swear to God. If there's one thing this government has been so effective at, it's tricking
you all into loving politicians, which is so weird and, and odd and distorted. So I'm blocking you.
Cut it out. All they did here was what they did with the monarchy in England. Y'all don't see that?
No, because the United States is so narrow-minded that we don't see what happens in other places
in order to identify how they're copying the same shit. The monarchy in England was made into
a literal celebrity. That's the only value they have to the audience. Because I mean, don't get me
wrong. They actually are locked in with the IMF and the World Bank, but to the people, they're nothing
except celebrity fodder. They fill up all of the tabloids. That's what they did here in the United
States with, with, with, with politicians. When you say, I love Mom Donnie, you are perpetuating the
problem. You don't know him. You don't have any real relationship with him. He serves no other
purpose than to represent you. And he has only been in office for three months and he has already won you
over. That's bonkers. That's bonkers. His father came to the U.S. on a CIA, to, to, to have a scholarship
in a CIA program. Bonkers. It's, it's not, how do I put this? The smartest thing to be is skeptical,
in my opinion. Like, I think at this point, our lack of skepticism is what has literally killed us
and killed so many of our comrades and killed so many people in other countries. It's because we
have been here in the United States being like, no, he has only been in office as governor. I mean,
as mayor for three months. I'm a New Yorker being head over heels for anybody is ridiculous. New
Yorkers voted for Eric Adams. Eric Adams got an office and showed y'all who the F he was.
Someone said talking about giving him a chance like they Sherry Headley on the six train and
coming to America. Give him a chance, honey. It doesn't matter if he was assembly member before
because now he's the mayor and what people are talking about is his tenure as mayor. They're
not talking about his tenure as assembly member. They have absolutely no idea what he was or wasn't
doing as an assembly member. No one ever makes any reference to any record of him as an assembly
member. None. I am Gemini. You don't find the negative. You find the problem. I mean,
absolutely. Foles will switch up. My loctician just switched up so crazy this week that I have
whiplash. People switch up. I've been the same nigga for the whole time, but people switch up.
They switch up. Fetterman and PA. People were phone banking for Fetterman only to find out he's a
bleeding heart Zionist and truly, truly was a plant. The loctician story.
I've already told the story. I feel like people tired of hearing this story.
I'm still so upset about it, but
Tay Vanderpump, it's like a decision. Tiffany, get me a male loctician in, please.
Fetterman is a plant. Like when you do protests, you become very adept at being able to spot cops.
And that's the thing that folks are not able to do in politicians. They're not able to spot a plant as
a politician. I have become able to, but only because of reading and listening and learning
and shitting up. Y'all want to hear the story about the loctician for real? Y'all in here like,
I want to hear it. I want to hear it. Oh man. It's going to take me a minute to get over it because
I really liked her as a person and she just broke my heart. She broke my heart.
Um, she had a shop, not a shop, but she had like a, like a studio. So it's like in a place that has
like a lot of different spaces and people can have like their own spot. Like they lease a spot instead
of leasing. Like it's like a coworking kind of, but for salons. Um, and so that's where I have been
coming to get my Murphy set. I'm nosy. Not gonna lie. Know yourself. I love that. Miss Debbie,
you'd have heard this story 50, 11 times. And Ms. Debbie's like, and I'm back again.
Um, she is also the person who I had a previous loctician who, who was a lot. She wasn't actually
a loctician. She was actually a liar and she had really messed up my hair. And, um, this sister
actually like contacted me and was like, I got you. And she really got me together and she formed my
locks. So it means something. It means a lot that she is the person who created my locks. Like
that matters. Okay. That matters. Like your locks are full of energy. They are coming from the,
the fascia that is closest to your brain. Your brain is the part that is connected. You know,
your soul is like what's making your brain work. Okay. So it's not a small thing. And, um,
um, so basically I have been going to her and we have wonderful, beautiful conversations and she
really just has like, um, a lot of like really like creative ideas when I would be talking about
different things. Like I read my book. She basically heard my whole book. Um, so we just spent a lot of
time together and I just really enjoyed her company and, um, um, I would go to her salon suite.
And so at the end of the year, last year, she decided that she was going to, um, end the lease
for her salon suite and, um, start doing house visits. She's been to my house before. Um, and so
I was like, Oh, okay. And so then in the top of the year, this year, she came to my house and did my
hair. Um, and so are y'all still listening? Cause I'm not going to keep going if you're not listening
anymore. Okay. Um, and so she, um, so I needed to get a, I needed to get my, my lot, as you can tell,
I needed to get my locks done. And I had just told her when I came back from Grenada that while I was
in Grenada, Arasta, um, had said, I went to Arasta had a setup, um, for his, um, for his fruits. And
when I went to go buy the fruits, he wasn't there. And so then someone had walked by and I was like,
you know, where Arasta and they said, Oh, well, um, you know, Arasta, he, he just probably walked
around, but he's going to come back. So I said, okay, well, there was a chair there. So I said,
well, let me just sit on the chair. So I sat down in the chair and waited for a while, but then no one
came. So then I just left him some money and I took my, um, I took my cocoa and my oranges and
went, and went, and went galang. Right. So then I came back later in the day to see if he was there.
Um, and I, I said, Arasta, you know, I left you seven, um, seven EC, but let me know if that was
enough because, um, I'm, you know, I'm not sure. And he said, you know, the teeth, the money man,
the teeth it. I was like, no, he said, but you know, someone had told me that Arasta woman was
waiting for me. Be still my beating heart. Arasta woman. And he was referring to me. Oh God.
I make it. I reach for Aguin, man. I reach for Aguin. So I was just over the moon. And so I texted her.
I was like, we are, we are anointed. We have been vetted by a, by a legend. I had made, um,
I had tried to meet with her when I came back. I had made an appointment to meet with her to get my
hair done the day I came back from Cuba because I had two events that I was going to do. And so
I was like, um, Oh, you know, do you have any openings? And she said, no, because she had to
go to the Oscars with one of her clients. But she was like, but if you can come to Harlem
on the 25th, um, if you, I don't, I have somebody later in the day. So if you can come to me,
I can get you done. And I said, fine, because she's making an accommodation for me. So then I know I
got to figure it out. So, but this would have been at her house and I don't like going to get my hair
done at hairstylists' homes because my experience with getting my hair done in hairstylists' homes
has not been a positive experience. Oftentimes it feels like I'm being kind of like fit in to
their life. Um, there's like a very, there's like a, it's kind of like there's a multitasking
happening that it ends up making the process longer. Um, and it's kind of like anything can
happen, you know, like I've been at someone's house and they got in like a full argument with
a man while I'm waiting to get my hair done. Um, you know, the kid is there and they back and forth
getting the kid done, you know, dealing with the kid and the kid can interrupt at any time,
et cetera, et cetera. Um, you know, sometimes they be answering the phone and having full
on conversations. Um, you know, there might be interruptions. Someone's coming to the door.
So like all of these things happen and no, listen, many of us, when we were in COVID got
to experience in real time, what it's like trying to work from home. Like you're at home.
There's just all types of shit that be going on. So I don't like going to people,
houses to get my hair done. They got the baby on the hip. Let me tell you one time I went to get
an edit done and a woman was breastfeeding while editing and people were, I made a comment about it
and people were like, you're so disrespectful to breastfeeders. No, first of all, you didn't tell
me he was going to be breastfeeding and you're charging me by the hour. So what, come on.
Um, so this was, um, something that I just like don't typically do, but I knew that this person
was, um, trying to accommodate me. So it's like, well, baby, you don't have to break out your
discomfort because they're making a, they're making a concession for you. Bet. So the day I got back from
Cuba though, I was so excited. Like it was like, I had been hit by a bus, me and my roommate in Cuba,
shout out to communal press. Both of us was like, Oh my God, we got to sleep. We got to sleep.
So I was like, um, but for the record, Murphy, I never voiced this. I never had to voice this because
I was never going to her house as a like constant. I was making the concession for myself. And so I
didn't need to like voice my boundaries because she's making a concession for me. And that's,
that's a conversation I need to have with myself. So, um, long story short, I was like, okay, I never
cancel, but I'm, I'm honestly, I'm going to have to cancel because I am so worn out that I really just
need to sleep. Um, and then the next day I got violently ill and was like vomiting and shitting.
And it was just like, great job, but you didn't go. Perfect. So fast forward. Um, she said, let me
know, you know, when we can reschedule. And I said, okay. And so she said, she picked a date and the date
was, uh, April 2nd. So Thursday, April 2nd. And so she said, you know, we'll do Thursday, April 2nd. I said,
cool. However, on Tuesday, she hit me Tuesday morning and said, sorry to spring this on you,
but my son is, um, not going to be in school on Thursday. And so I'm not going to be able to come
to you on Thursday. Um, and so I was like, well, I can't come on Thursday. And I thought that she was
saying this based on her son, because that's how she framed it. Um, and she said, okay, then I'll come
to you on Wednesday. Is that okay? And I said, yes. So then I said, yes, no April fools. That was my
exact words. So then on Wednesday, I mean, so then later that day she hit me and said, okay, we're
close. I can't come to you on Wednesday because I can't come to you on Wednesday because I have to get
my son off to school and coming to you before 9am. It's just going to be a lot for me. She's done this
before, but I guess right now it just is a lot for her. So she, for whatever reason, she didn't
specify that, but she just said it would be a lot for her. Then she said, um, plus I have a doctor's
appointment at two o'clock. So I need you to come to me so that I can get to my doctor's appointment on
time. Um, if you, uh, otherwise we are leaving. Otherwise I'm available on Monday. However, my son
will not be in school. So you'd still have to come to me. And I believe her son is like nine,
10 or 11, like there, but I know that he like walks home from school. He has a key around his neck.
Like he lets himself in the apartment. Like, so he does have, you know, the autonomy, um,
the autonomy and independence. So she said, you know, Monday, my son will not be in school.
So I also won't be available Tuesday. We leave for Costa Rica for a week. Um, and then we'll be
back on the 20th. We'll be back on the 21st, but I'm booked up. And so I wouldn't have availability
again for like another week after that. So which I replied on text. Here's the thing.
Previously, you said that you were making house calls and now it feels like the only options I'm
being given are for me to come to you or not get my hair done for three weeks. And for me to come to
you requires, I got to board my dog. Also, um, I'm going to be, I'm going to be, I have to pay for
travel, et cetera. And, um, you know, it's, I'm going to tell you my exact words actually.
Here's the thing. You said the new setup was you traveling. And now the only options I'm being
given is me traveling and waiting three weeks to get my hair done. I really feel like me making
the trek based on childcare is not really fair. I then have to board my dog for the day and it
becomes another expense and pay for travel. He's more than welcome to come with you to my home.
Um, someone in here said so far, this doesn't sound like enough to leave her alone. First of all,
you're a people pleaser and you need to think about that because, um, actually I should have left her
alone at this point because this, what she's doing is complete manipulation. Her son has nothing to do
with me. Her son has nothing to do with me. I'm paying $450 for the service. And ultimately it's
based on you and setting your, Oh, you, you, you gotta go. Ultimately it's based on you setting the
scenario and expectations. So if you set the expectations, I'm simply just responding to the
expectations that you upset. Um, and you know, I'm saying like you can bring your son. I've had
hairstylists bring their kids to my house before. So she replied back with a very, very, very, very long
essay text. Now, remember, this is somebody that I consider to be a friend. She's been to my house
for a gathering. Um, no, her son has not been to my house before because she drops him off at school
before she comes and does my hair. And she's never had an issue doing it before, but all of a sudden
this is the issue. Um, and someone said, I love your high expectations. This, these are not high
expectations. These are very basic expectations of simply just professionalism. And I am a very big
believer that we can be friends and professionals. I want to pay my friends. I want to pay my friends
for the work they do. I love being able to support my friends professionally. This whole idea that we
can't be friends and we can't get informal is so colonialism coded. It's capitalism coded. We should
absolutely be able to respect each other and be friends and also hold each other in, um,
and hold each other in professionalism. That, that is to me like basic. And if she had said,
listen, I just don't want to come up there, then say that. However, the flip of the script to
manipulate me is not cool. And ultimately the real thing that you do, if you actually care about the
friendship is you say, I know I said I wasn't going to come up there. So I'm going to figure it
out this time. However, I'm not going to do it no more. Cause I just realized I don't want to do it
no more. That's it. That's it. That's how you deal with people that you actually give a fuck about.
So she sent me a very, very long text that I didn't read. Cause I was like at the length of
it, I was so like, Oh my gosh, I guess we're like having an argument. And, um, who said anything
about autism having to do with high expectations? Who, who, who on this chat said anything about
autism having anything to do with high expectations? I didn't, I didn't see anybody, anybody else here.
So when you add, I say this with love, it's very condescending. Um, so any who I pick up the phone
because I'm a millennial, I'm a millennial. So I'm going to pick up the phone. If I see
what looks like someone is upset, I'm going to pick up the phone. If I see that, it looks like I have
been missing, misrepresented or misinterpreted because text has a way of doing that. So we need
to get on the phone quick. You know what I'm saying? Quick. We got to get on the phone.
That's how I exist. And that's on both ends. If I share with somebody that I'm upset, you need to
call me. You need to call me. And if somebody shares with me that they're upset, I'm going to
call you because we need to get analog quick. We need to get human to human, ideally face to face.
But if that's not, that's not available, then we got to talk. So I pick up the phone and I was like,
what is this long text you sending me? Are you, you know, it sounds like, um, I said,
why didn't you just call me? So you didn't read the text. And I was like, oh, what's this tone?
And I was like, nah, I didn't read the text because, um, it was so long. And I was just like,
you know, this is a lot. So, um, are you okay? Like, it sounds like you're upset. No, I'm not upset.
I'm not upset. Actually. I didn't even know that she had this person in her. We've never
had a disagreement. So I've never met this person, but I did write you an entire text. So if you're
calling to vent, you could have just gotten all the information you needed from the text.
I said, well, I'm not calling to vent. I'm calling because I don't want to like interpret your tone.
I'd rather just hear from you. And I would also just want to talk to you because you know, we're on
text. Well, I'm basically just going to read everything that I wrote. So if that's what you
want me to do to just read what I wrote in the text, then fine. I was like, I don't understand why
you're behaving like this. And I'm saying it, I'm giving you all my exact tone because I don't want
to misinterpret. I don't want to pretend like I was like really calm, cool. Cause I wasn't, I was like,
what's going on right now. I was like, why are you even talking how I'm behaving? Yeah. How you're
behaving? Like how, why are you behaving like this with me? Like I'm literally calling you because I'm
trying to figure out what's going on. And you know, you're telling me you're not upset, but you're
acting like someone who is upset. I'm not upset, Amanda. I have set my boundary and you have set your
boundary. So how, where, you know, where do we go from here? I said, do we even need to go anywhere
from here? Well, are we talking as friends or are we talking as someone who is a client?
Because you did throw out the professional element. So how, how, how do you want to proceed?
Because I'm actually being very patient. I had no idea that this person could treat me like that.
And every day that's gone by since I'm more and more disturbed. Cause it's, it's fucked up.
It's actually fucked up. And I loved her. So we're clear. I loved her. She has always only shown me
a beautiful person. So to see this shadow come about, I'm getting emotional. So I was genuinely just like,
I'm not really sure what's going on here. And I just really feel like this is not really making
any sense. Like I'm trying to like move forward. And, uh, well, you know, can I talk? Can I talk?
I'm like, I'm not even, what are we, we're having a conversation. No, now you're trying to dominate.
I'm not trying to dominate nothing. What are we, what is going on? Well, I am like, what,
what do you want moving forward? What, what, what, like, I've already told you that I'm not
available. And now you're telling me that you're not available. And I was just like, I don't even
understand this. And, oh, now you're, can I talk? I'm like, you were just talking. And she was like,
well, you know, if you called here to get your rocks off, I'm like, your rocks off. What are you
talking about? And I want to say this to the people saying, coming up with all these, like,
maybe she's this, maybe she's that. That's not our jobs. We do not have to do that. We do not have
to do that. We're over 40. We do not have to do that. I don't have space to science someone else's
shadows. I'm trying to science the shadows that are energy farming from us that are creating the
impending doom on earth. So I don't have the time, the bandwidth, like they like to say, I don't have
that for anybody, including my mother. I'm like, I'm not doing that with you. The second I feel like
I got to science out your shadows. We're not talking until I re until I've like restored
because I'm not doing it. I'm just not. That's why we can no longer give space to people who are
giving space to their shadows. Do the work. You know how much work I do and have done on my shadows
on, on the, and your shadows, by the way, in my interpretation, your shadows are these like
cancer cells of your soul that are created. It's like, they're, they're like,
your shadows are kind of like soul gremlins that are created from trauma and they come to life.
You know how gremlins come to life at night? Your shadows, your shadow gremlins come to light
when certain triggers happen. And so you have to work on how to understand all of your individual
shadow gremlins. You have to work to then understand what is the thing that you do that responds to them
and has you speaking through your trauma. That is hard work. And it also is, and it's hard work
because you get to see how you are fucking up. You get to see how you're being an asshole. You get to
see how you are perpetuating the same shit that you hate being done to you. And you go through your
own shame of like, am I really acting like that? Was I really acting like that? Yes, it is liberating.
And when you do that work and you get to the other side of that, it becomes so much easier to then begin
the work of the world of seeing the shadows that are at work in the world. So many of the folks that
I know that refuse to acknowledge what's actually happening in this world have not done real shadow
work. It breaks you. And Christine, I feel you. Murphy, you are one more dumbass comment away from being
blocked. So, you know, the real effort is being able to, you know, see your whole self
in order to restore. So the real work is being able to see the whole self you've become in order
to restore the soul that arrived. Stop telling me that I hold stylists in a high regard. What are you
even talking about? You don't even know any other stylists that I know or how I regard them. So what are
you saying? That's the work. This world has shaped the soul into something else. You have to then
restore that soul. It's hard work. Someone in here said she held resentments against me that I didn't
know. And it's like, I can't relate to that because I don't hold resentments against people that they don't
know about. I'm not going to pretend, you know, I don't hold resentments against people. I also don't
like sarcasm, by the way. I dish it, but I don't like, I don't take it. I do not hold resentments
against people that they don't know about because who has the time and space for that? If I have a
resentment against you, we're going to talk about it. If it can't be talked about, then we'll just let
go. And if her idea of me change, I don't know what did it. I have an idea, but I'm not even going
to put that on blast here because it's, I'm not even trying to expose her identity. Like that's how
I'm like being respectful. And once I say what I'm going to say, it reposes her identity. And it's like,
so, you know, that, that, um, Tiffany, that's probably it. Um, so then I just, um, I, you know,
I, when she told me that she was being patient with me, um, I say, you know what, I'm gonna just
call it. Is she afraid to voice her opinion? What's her opinion? Her opinion of me? Someone
says she'll be back with an apology soon. She's blocked. When I got off the phone, um,
I went to her page and she had already unfollowed me. So something I had said previously or whatever.
So basically she was like pretending, I guess. Um, me and you both, Ebony, me and you both.
Um, oh my God, Laurel. I literally said on the phone when I said like how you're behaving and
she was like, what do you mean how I'm behaving? I said, you're placating.
Laurel be like right here with me, right here. Um, are you ready for the Michael movie? No.
Yeah. She thought she was right. That's how it go. So that was that. Um,
so Instagram is now kicking me off of live. So there we are. That's the story of things. And,
um, I just want you guys to stay fortified and, um, Taisha, what Laurel is telling you is the correct
answer. So read that. That's exactly what I would have said. Um, and you know, putting me as like
some transaction, like she could afford to lose me that, that to me is not, that is, that frames me
as if I am simply just a transaction and nothing about our interaction at that point was a transaction.
So something else was happening that has nothing to do with me. And that's why it's very,
that's why you can't like take things personal. Um, and that's that. So that was a story that y'all
wanted to hear. So the story has been told, um, again, stay lifted, stay fortified. April,
according to the astrology girlies, it's about to kick our butts. It's about to be incredibly
challenging. It's about to really push the limits of your conviction and commitment. And so we have
to remember to stay fortified in the bottom line. And so I want all of you all to ask yourself,
what is the bottom line to that, which you are committed to that thesis is what you're going to
have to make sure that you come back to every time. And I will close with this, Laurel. I don't think I
was connected deeper than her. I think just as a soul, I am connected deeper than her. And that is why
in this moment of dissension, I was able to still see her as a person. And she was not,
you all be blessed. Have a good night and stay clear headed. Don't let them get you.